export function allQuestions(){
    return (
        [
            {   
                question: "in HTML, a tag used as an alternative to make text bold is",
                options: {
                    a: "<bold>", b: "<double>", c: "<strong>", d: "<dark>"
                },
                answer: "<strong>"
            },
            {  
                question: "In HTML forms, form elements are different type of",
                options: {
                    a: "Input elements", b: "Text fields", c: "Submit buttons", d: "All of the Above"
                },
                answer: "All of the Above"
            },
            {   
                question: "A tag known to be fundamental HTML block is",
                options: {
                    a: "<!DOCTYPE>", b: "<HTML>", c: "<BODY>", d: "<P>"
                },
                answer: "<HTML>"
            },
            {   
                question: "Defining a special style for special table, the added attribute should be of",
                options: {
                    a: "<class>", b: "<padding>", c: "<id>", d: "<tr>"
                },
                answer: "<id>"
            },
            {   
                question: "In HTML, the element <html> defines the",
                options: {
                    a: "Element", b: "Function", c: "Whole document", d: "Content"
                },
                answer: "Whole document"
            },
            {   
                question: "The number of attributes required for <div> element, is/are of",
                options: {
                    a: 0, b: 1, c: 2, d: 3
                },
                answer: 0
            },
            {   
                question: "A client side script is defined by the tag",
                options: {
                    a: "<clientscript>", b: "<script>", c: "<jcscript>", d: "<javascript>"
                },
                answer: "<script>"
            },
            {  
                question: "The default display value for most of the HTML elements are",
                options: {
                    a: "Block", b: "Inline", c: "External", d: "A and B"
                },
                answer: "A and B"
            },
            {   
                question: "Element used as a container for other HTML elements known as",
                options: {
                    a: "<id>", b: "<div>", c: "<class>", d: "<span>"
                },
                answer: "<div>"
            },
            {   
                question: "The HTML element known to be <del>, defines",
                options: {
                    a: "Deleted data", b: "Removed data", c: "Crossed data", d: "Overwritten data"
                },
                answer: "Removed data"
            },
            {   
                question: "In Javascript, the data type of an array is",
                options: {
                    a: "Char", b: "int", c: "object", d: "NaN"
                },
                answer: "object"
            },
            {   
                question: "In HTML, a specific style for a special element can be defined by the attribute",
                options: {
                    a: "<style>", b: "<header>", c: "<id>", d: "<special>"
                },
                answer: "<id>"
            },
            {   
                question: "In Javascript, the data type of NaN is",
                options: {
                    a: "Null", b: "Undefined", c: "Character", d: "Number"
                },
                answer: "Number"
            },
            {   
                question: "In HTML, the unvisited links are specified in color",
                options: {
                    a: "Purple", b: "Red", c: "Blue", d: "Green"
                },
                answer: "Blue"
            },
            {   
                question: "An array method named splice() is used for",
                options: {
                    a: "Insertion", b: "Deletion", c: "Updation", d: "Length retrieving"
                },
                answer: "Insertion"
            },
            {   
                question: "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
                options: {
                    a: "<scripting>", b: "<javascript>", c: "<script>", d: "<js>"
                },
                answer: "<script>"
            },
            {   
                question: "Among the following, which one is a ternary operator?",
                options: {
                    a: "+", b: ":", c: "-", d: "?:"
                },
                answer: "?:"
            },
            {   
                question: "Which of the following is not a valid javascript variable name?",
                options: {
                    a: "2names", b: "_first_and_last", c: "FirstAndLast", d: "None of the above"
                },
                answer: "2names"
            },
            {   
                question: "Which of the following is not considered as javascript operator?",
                options: {
                    a: "new", b: "this", c: "delete", d: "typeof"
                },
                answer: "this"
            },
            {  
                question: "Which method evaluates a string of Javascript code in the context of the specified object?",
                options: {
                    a: "Eval", b: "ParseInt", c: "ParseFloat", d: "Efloat"
                },
                answer: "Eval"
            },
            {  
                question: "Which of the following event fires when the form element loses the focus on its child elements",
                options: {
                    a: "onfocus", b: "onblur", c: "onclick", d: "ondbclick"
                },
                answer: "onblur"
            },
            {  
                question: "Which statement is used to test for a specific condition",
                options: {
                    a: "Select", b: "If", c: "Switch", d: "For"
                },
                answer: "If"
            },
            {  
                question: "The ______ method of an array object adds and/or removes elements from an array",
                options: {
                    a: "Reverse", b: "Shift", c: "Slice", d: "Splice"
                },
                answer: "Splice"
            },
            {  
                question: "Choose the client-side javascript object:",
                options: {
                    a: "Database", b: "Cursor", c: "Client", d: "FileUpload"
                },
                answer: "FileUpload"
            },
            {  
                question: "What will be the output of 2+5+'8'",
                options: {
                    a: 258, b: "Error", c: 7, d: 78
                },
                answer: 78
            },
            {  
                question: "Which of the following is not a reserved word in JavaScript?",
                options: {
                    a: "interface", b: "throws", c: "program", d: "short"
                },
                answer: "program"
            },
            {   
                question: "The 'function' and 'var' are known as:",
                options: {
                    a: "Keywords", b: "Data types", c: "Declaration statements", d: "Prototypes"
                },
                answer: "Declaration statements"
            },
            {   
                question: "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
                options: {
                    a: "Global variable", b: "The local element", c: "The two of the above", d: "None of the above"
                },
                answer: "The local element"
            },
            {   
                question: "In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:",
                options: {
                    a: "Syntax error", b: "Missing of semicolons", c: "Division by zero", d: "Missing of Bracket"
                },
                answer: "Division by zero"
            },
            {   
                question: "Choose the correct snippet from the following to check if the variable 'a' is not equal the 'NULL':",
                options: {
                    a: "if(a!==null)", b: "if (a!)", c: "if(a!null)", d: "if(a!=null)"
                },
                answer: "if(a!==null)"
            }
        ]
    )

}